When he talks, women listen.
The Guru is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Daisy von Scherler Mayer.
Bored with Bollywood movies but fascinated with their Hollywood counterparts from his youth, Ram
dreams to become a singer and actor in America, the country where dreams are made.
He is encouraged when his American-based close friend, Vijay Rao, comes for
visit, and brags about driving a Mercedes and living in a penthouse.
Ramu Gupta, played by Jimi Mistry.
Sharonna, played by Heather Graham.
Lexi, played by Marisa Tomei.
Dwain, played by Michael McKean.
Rusty McGee, played by Dash Mihok.
Vijay Rao, played by Emil Marwa.
The Guru is a 2002 sex comedy film written by Tracey Jackson
and directed by Daisy von Scherler Mayer.
The film centres on a dance teacher who comes to the United States from India to pursue a normal career but incidentally stumbles into
a brief but high-profile career as a sex guru, a career based on a philosophy he learns from a pornographic actress.
The film stars Jimi Mistry as the eponymous character, Heather Graham as the actress he learns from, and
Marisa Tomei, who helps him reach his guru status among her socialite New York City friends.
The film explores themes of new love, dancing master, porn actor, guru, wedding.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.